[
    {
      "question": "The .container class provides a full width container, spanning the entire width of the screen",
      "option": [
        "False",
        "True"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class provides a responsive fixed width container?",
      "option": [
        ".container",
        ".container-fluid",
        ".container-fixed"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which contextual class is used to create an orange text color?",
      "option": [
        ".bg-warning",
        ".text-warning",
        ".txt-warning",
        ".txt-orange"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "The Bootstrap grid system is based on how many columns?",
      "option": [
        "12",
        "9",
        "3",
        "6"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class adds zebra-stripes to a table?",
      "option": [
        ".table-bordered",
        ".table-zebra",
        ".table-striped",
        ".even and .odd"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class shapes an image to a circle?",
      "option": [
        ".img-round",
        ".rounded-circle",
        ".img-circle",
        ".img-rounded"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class is used to create a big box for calling extra attention?",
      "option": [
        ".jumbotron",
        ".container",
        ".bigbox"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which button class is used to create a large button?",
      "option": [
        ".btn-lg",
        ".btn-l",
        ".btn-large",
        ".btn-xl"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class is used to create a button group?",
      "option": [
        ".button-group",
        ".group-btn",
        ".btn-group",
        ".group-button"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class is used to create a badge?",
      "option": [
        ".badge-item",
        ".badge-label",
        ".badge",
        ".label-badge"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class is used to create a loader?",
      "option": [
        ".spinner-border",
        ".loader",
        ".spinner",
        ".spinner-loader"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class is used to create a basic pagination?",
      "option": [
        ".pagination",
        ".page",
        ".pages",
        ".navigation"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class is used to create a basic list group?",
      "option": [
        ".list-group",
        ".group-list",
        ".grouped-list"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class adds a heading to a card?",
      "option": [
        ".card-footer",
        ".card-heading",
        ".card-header",
        ".card-head"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class indicates a dropdown menu?",
      "option": [
        ".dropdown-list",
        ".dropdown",
        ".select"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "A standard navigation tab is created with:",
      "option": [
        "<ul class=\"nav nav-tabs\">",
        "<ul class=\"nav tabs\">",
        "<ul class=\"nav nav-navbar\">",
        "<ul class=\"navigation-tabs\">"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "A standard navigation bar is created with:",
      "option": [
        "<nav class=\"navbar navbar-default\">",
        "<nav class=\"navigationbar navbar-default\">",
        "<nav class=\"navbar navbar-expand-sm\">",
        "<nav class=\"nav navbar\">"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class is used to create a vertical navigation bar?",
      "option": [
        ".navbar-inverse",
        ".navbar navbar-vertical",
        ".navbar",
        ".navbar-vertical"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which component is used to cycle through elements, like a slideshow?",
      "option": [
        "Scrollspy",
        "Slideshow",
        "Carousel",
        "Orbit"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What classes can be combined to create a custom checkbox?",
      "option": [
        "checkbox control",
        "custom-control custom-checkbox",
        "custom-check custom-checkbox"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which attribute is used to create a tooltip?",
      "option": [
        "data-toggle=\"popup\"",
        "data-toggle=\"tooltip\"",
        "data-toggle=\"collapse\"",
        "data-toggle=\"modal\""
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which contextual class indicates a succesful or positive action?",
      "option": [
        ".bg-success",
        ".bg-warning",
        ".bg-primary",
        ".bg-info"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which contextual class indicates a dangerous or potentially negative action?",
      "option": [
        ".bg-warning",
        ".bg-info",
        ".bg-danger",
        ".bg-primary"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class indicates uppercased text?",
      "option": [
        ".ucase",
        ".uppercase",
        ".text-capitalize",
        ".text-uppercase"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "The Bootstrap grid system works across multiple devices.",
      "option": [
        "False",
        "True"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    }
  ]